

ENO ATTE

<u>So</u>ftware Engineer

+234 8063611790

attegift@gmail.com

Port Harcourt/Rivers State/Nig.

eno-atte-87b738164

https://royalbrainsms.com

ABOUT ME

Full stack Web Developer specializing in front Believes in self and back end development. Experienced with descipline, deligency and all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages.

a proactive teamwork

Very Inovative and Strong Descision maker

SKILLS

Laravel-PHP

Skill Name

Express js-NODE

Skill Name

React Js, Vue Js

Skill Name

MongoDB, Mysql

Skill Name

Java,Javas

EDUCATION

B.Sc. Maths/Computer

University Of Port Harcourt 2009-2014

Senior School Certificate

Comprehensive Secondary School, Okobo. Aks 1998-1997

First School Leaving

Government Primary School, Uko-Uyukim, Oron 1991-1997

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Thinkschool Technology/Lagos State/2019-2021

Development/Management Of Web Applications

- Technical Manager
- Developer

MERN Stack Developer

Quadria Limited/Port Harcourt/2016-2018

Development/Management Of Web Applications

React/Node Developer

ICT Instructor

Christi L'eco/Port Harcourt/2015-2016

Head Of ICT Department

Mathematics/ICT Teacher

PROJECTS ACCOMPLISHED

Design/develops/management of:

- School Management Software(Thinkschoolapp)
- Computer Based Test System(Royalbrain CBT System).
- E-commerce Application and other web applications/websites.